Robert Alsobrook

Email: lastgulch@gmail.com

Web: buffbob.com

Phone: 303-519-0549

PERSONAL ENDEAVORS

2015-Present-- A devoted volunteer for Wildlife 2000. A world-renowned beaver relocation group located in Denver

2010-Present-- Have donated over 50 bison to various Native American tribes for food and for reintroduction efforts. Hosted a

2005-2015-- Served on the board of the Southern Plains Land Trust. Hosted school groups for educational purposes.

2008-2018-- Provided retirement care for bison from the Denver Zoo.

WORK HISTORY

1999-present-- Bison Rancher

1992-present- Carpenter

1995-1999 Owner/Backcountry Pizza

EDUCATION

University of Colorado-Boulder

1993- Chemistry BS, Biology BA

WHAT I DO FOR FUN

Inline skate, telemark, backpack and trail run with my border collie, playing tennis with my daughter, gardening, raft camping, not finding a job:)

SUMMARY

After 25 years of hard labor and a severe back injury I thought I would learn another trade. I have no relevant work experience so I have made a website **BuffBob.com** that shows my talents. I built the website from python and flask and maintain the server for it and other programs found at that site. It has links to other webapps, code projects, my github and dockerhub, and other links. I built this page to act as the main way to display my talents given that I may have arrived here from a different path than most and a resume kinda seems pointless.

Relevant Computer Skills

Strong Data Analysis chops with python

Machine and Deep Learning with Tensorflow/keras, TensorflowJS, scikit-learn

Strong core java 9+ skills. Beginner experience with java web programming.

The basics of front end web development. Intermediate python/ Flask backend skills

open source GIS, remote sensing and imagery including lidar

The basics- Git, Linux, some server, sql, docker...

Some experience with other languages-- Lua, Octave, C, Julia, and Russian...

What makes me a good hire

A true problem solver- 'jerryrig' should be my middle name. My ranch was 75 miles from the nearest town. This tends to make one not only self sufficient but a problem solver. Better to figure out a unique solution and avoid a drive to town for a certain part.. This was very similar to how I learned to program from the internet. No professors, office hours, etc. If I had a question I figured it out online and through trial and error.

I am fun, a good conversationalist, and have a diverse base of knowledge. I know Colorado and the West very well. I do wish I could write better. This was perhaps my motivation for creating TweestMasters.com.

Please visit BuffBob.com to see my work